game.com.au 2008-12-17

# Welcome to GAME - The Next Level

Privacy Policy

**Respecting your privacy and upholding the law**  
The privacy and security of your personal information has always been of the utmost importance to us at GAME. We are committed to respecting your right to privacy and protecting your personal information. We are bound by the National Privacy Principles in the Privacy Act 1988 (Commonwealth) and any relevant Privacy Principles under NSW state legislation, as well as other applicable laws and codes affecting your personal information. Our staff are trained to respect your privacy in accordance with our standards, policies and procedures.

GAME is TGW Pty. Limited along with any other subsidiaries, franchise operations or members of the GAME retail organisation.

**About this privacy policy  
**This Privacy Policy outlines how we collect and manage personal information provided to us by our customers.

This document also describes the sorts of information held and for what purposes, as well as how that information is collected, held, used and disclosed.

Our Privacy Policy applies to all your dealings with us whether at one of our retail stores, through our 13 4263 (13 GAME) number or via our website and/or e-mail transmissions.

We encourage you to check www.game.com.au regularly for any updates to our Privacy Policy.

**Collecting your personal information**     
Depending on the product or service obtained, GAME will collect and hold your personal information for the purposes of:

  * Monitoring sales data/history with the intention of providing special offers or loyalty discounts.
  * Managing and administering the product or service obtained from GAME.

Your personal information may also be collected for the purpose of letting you know about products or services offered by GAME that might interest you along with promotions or other opportunities in which you may be interested.

The information collected includes, but is not limited to, your name, postal or email address, phone number(s), date of birth, transaction history with GAME or other information the organisation considers necessary.

We will only collect your personal information directly from you. This may happen whenever you purchase a product or service, or submit an administrative form (eg a change of address form), or when you give us personal information over the telephone or counter, or via our website. 

**Using and disclosing your personal information     
**GAME will not disclose your personal information to any external party or individual under any circumstances unless required to by Federal or State laws where applicable. Any information obtained by us is stored on stand-alone computer equipment not connected to a network or Internet connection. From time to time, we may approach you on behalf of a third-party vendor or supplier. Rest assured that your details have not been forwarded to any other parties outside GAME, as all correspondence (including data compilation, layout, printing and mailing) is done in-house.

**Marketing practices and ethics**     
It is our practice to seek your consent to use your personal information in order to let you know about, and develop, products and services that might better serve your needs or promotions or other opportunities in which you may be interested. This may be done after your initial contact with us. At the point of initial contact, a GAME representative will ask you whether you wish to receive correspondence from us on a regular basis. Should you wish to be removed from any future mailing lists at a later date, or simply do not want to be contacted by us, please notify your closest GAME store on 13 4263 (13 GAME).

**Gaining access to personal information held by us.  
**You may be able to gain access to any personal information held by us. This is subject to some exceptions as governed by Federal, State and Territory law. Factors affecting a right to access include:

  * Access would pose a serious threat to the life or health of any individual.
  * Access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of others.
  * A frivolous or vexatious request.
  * The information relates to a commercially sensitive decision making process.
  * Access would be unlawful.
  * Any legal dispute resolution proceedings whether involving GAME or not.
  * Denying access is required or authorised by or under law.

We will give you reasons if we deny access.

Contact us to request access (see 'Contacting Us' below). In some cases we may be able to deal with your request over the telephone or over the counter at one of our retail stores.

**Resolving your privacy issues   **  
If you have any issues or concerns you wish to raise with us, or would simply like to discuss any issues about our Privacy Policy, then you are able to do so a number of ways:

  * You are welcome to speak directly to our sales staff and they will endeavour to resolve your issue first-hand. If further action is required we will keep you advised of any progress made. If our staff are unable to resolve the matter, it will be escalated as appropriate to facilitate a resolution. We take the matter of safeguarding your privacy very seriously and will act on any suspected breach of policy.
  * You can call us on 13 4263 (13 GAME) or (02) 9659-2222 any time between 9am and 5pm Monday to Friday EST.
  * You can e-mail your question/issue to us at [privacy@game.com.au](mailto:privacy@game.com.au).

**Contacting Us  
**For more information about our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@game.com.au](mailto:privacy@game.com.au).

For more information about privacy in general, you can visit the Federal Privacy Commissioner's website: [www.privacy.gov.au.](http://www.privacy.gov.au/)

To download a copy of this document in Adobe Acrobat (PDF) format, [click here.](http://www.game.com.au/downloads/game_privacy0108.pdf)

You may require [Adobe Acrobat Reader](http://www.adobe.com/products/acrobat/readstep2.html) to view this document.
